The dull and production -inhibiting summer is finally over
And EFN stock exchange lunch is back.
Today Monday 12 August we have plenty to talk about.
Come along.
Heavy the CEO, a turbulent outside world
And two lead -heavy guests in the studio.
Welcome Fredrik Skoglund and Mattias Eriksson.
Has summer been good
Yes I think so.
-giantbra.
But the stock exchange wasn't the top?
-Very volatile.
No further report period either.
-You have some pictures.
Toilet paper, diapers ... It is difficult to find similar products on the Stockholm Stock Exchange.
Attractive.
Grows steadily over time with a marginal improvement trip ahead.
Pay expensive for quality on the stock exchange
So it is on the stock exchange at the moment.
Some "Compounders" ...
Essity may not be that expensive, but some compounders are swindling.
While the cyclical companies get "whip" when there is concern about the brandy cure.
So will we continue with compounders
Or should the cyclical ...?
Maybe there is a valuation bottom.
The hope is that when the stock market drops for various reasons ...
Economic turmoil, Trump tweets ...
When everything goes down, you can pick up quality companies at a low valuation.